<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root> 
    <cn>这是一款针对儿童的有趣的填色绘画软件， 可以让孩子选择不同的颜色直接在线稿图上涂色，创作出属于自己的美妙绝伦的绘画作品。丰富渐变的颜色，发挥孩子的想象力，让孩子感受绘画及色彩的乐趣

幼儿从小对一切新鲜事物都会感到好奇心，特别对于画画更是有着浓厚的兴趣，从开始的涂鸦期开始就表现出了幼儿对画画的兴趣是很深厚的。而且画画对于幼儿、儿童来说是百利而无一害。从小培养幼儿画画培养儿童画画对孩子的成长是我们无法想像的

孩子在绘画过程中的构思、构图、造型、涂色、修整……从始至终所有的全过程，（无论是动手还是动脑）都是完完全全独立完成而且永远不能和其他人一样。从某种意义上来讲，在孩子的童年时代，在独立思考与独立工作的训练上，没有任何一种活动能与画画相比

儿童在成长的阶段，外面世界对于他们来说都是新鲜的，好奇心可以让他们对世界万物充满兴趣。而这一点正是少儿绘画的动力源泉。他们喜欢把眼中的新鲜事物通过画笔描绘出来。一个细小的事物，孩子们要通过自己的观察，发现它们更具体的结构组成，更丰富的颜色变化，这样才能把事物最本质和最传神的美描绘出来。这种观察方法也可以大大提高理性思维和逻辑推理能力。

娱乐是小孩子的天性，也是他的权利。没有足够的娱乐，小孩身心不可能健康发展。绘画是他们最喜欢的娱乐方式之一，同时也是最安全、最经济、最高尚、对身心健康最有利的娱乐。

小朋友们拿起你的画笔一起创作美丽的图画吧，图画完成后可以跟爸爸妈妈或者小伙伴们分享，看看谁的画作更可爱更漂亮哦！
  
我们产品的特点：
1，产品涵盖100多种动物图片以及100+颜色选择。
2，采用独特的涂色技术，可让孩子们在图案上涂色不会出界。
3，绘画可以保存下来，下次可以选择继续作画。 
4，图案精美，符合图像式学习的视觉需求，加深记忆
5，我们产品的开发人员本身也是孩子的家长，更加关心孩子的成长，同时我们也请来了育儿专家一起来设计这款应用。
    </cn>


    <en>This is a children's interesting color painting software, can let the children choose different colors directly online manuscript painting, created their own wonderful paintings. Enrich the color of the gradual change, give full play to the imagination of the children, and let the children feel the pleasure of painting and color
Young children are curious about all kinds of new things, especially for drawing. From the beginning of the graffiti period, children show interest in drawing. And painting for children and children is a hundred profit and no harm. It is unthinkable for us to cultivate children's painting from childhood to cultivate children's painting.
Children conception, composition, shape, color, in the process of painting dressing...... All the whole process from beginning to end, (either yourself or brains) are completely independent and can never be like other people. In a sense, in the children's childhood, in the training of independent thinking and independent work, no activity can be compared to painting.
In the stage of children's growth, the outside world is fresh to them, and curiosity can make them interested in all things in the world. And this is the power source of children's painting. They like to paint the fresh things in their eyes through a brush. A small thing, children must find their more specific structural composition and richer color changes through their own observation, so that we can depict the most essential and most vivid beauty of things. This method of observation can also greatly improve the ability of rational thinking and logical reasoning.
Entertainment is the nature of a child and his right. Without enough entertainment, children can't develop physically and mentally. Painting is one of their favorite forms of entertainment, and it is also the safest, most economical, noblest, and most favorable to physical and mental health.
The children pick up your brush and create beautiful pictures together. After the picture is finished, you can share with your parents or your friends. See whose paintings are more lovely and beautiful.
The features of our products:
1, the product covers more than 100 animal pictures and 100+ color selection.
2, the unique painting technique, can let the children paint on the pattern will not be out of bounds.
3, painting can be preserved, the next time you can choose to continue to draw.
4, the pattern is fine, conforms to the visual needs of the image learning, and deepens the memory.
5, the developers of our products are also the parents of their children. They are more concerned about their children's growth. Meanwhile, we have invited parenting experts to design this application.
    </en>

</root>
