<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root> 
    <cn>
        这是一款专为婴幼儿设计的识物应用,亲子早教游戏，并且深入地了解它们！各种益智游戏，幼儿习惯培养，兴趣培养，同时也是一款全新的互动式识字卡游戏。
家庭育儿益智启蒙教育必备的免费儿童游戏，互动学习，通过实物图片,让宝宝更早学会识别生活中的事物，轻松学习各种动物卡和声音... ...从视觉听觉触觉三方面进行启蒙教育，让宝宝在游戏中轻松认知。

简单地按一下，就可以看到许多图片及听到各种声音。通过 100多 种涵盖动物、乐器、车辆等方面的声音和图像锻炼孩子的触觉、视觉和听觉。 只需轻按一下某个动物或物品即可看其图像，听其名称，观其拼写。 这是为小朋友的游戏时间所准备的一款完美学习工具。

高清晰度的图片明亮而生动，声音质量亦极佳。 我们提供了 6 类图片 - 包括家养动物、野生动物、乐器、车辆、家用物品和风景名胜 - 这些精彩的图片将满足孩子们的好奇心而总是令人爱不释手。 乐器类尤其可以带来许多乐趣。 每种乐器提供的音乐曲子，还可能会让你跟着轻轻摇晃！

－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－
 
游戏特色：
*互动学习游戏。
*安全而易于操作， 轻按一下即可玩。
*适合孩子的引人入胜的学习环境，包括清晰又漂亮的图片和有趣的声音。
*配对游戏：针对0-3岁宝宝精心设计的益智游戏，培养宝宝的判断能力。 
*丰富有趣的产品让孩子在游戏中独立思考，自由学习，享受探索世界的乐趣。


我们专注于儿童游戏产品的研发，根据不同年龄段宝宝的成长特点，精心打造专属的幼儿产品，交互方式独特，以达到教育的目的和效果启蒙，为宝宝的童年增添了一抹亮丽的门，有利于孩子的健康身体和智力发育，智力发展和完善，在娱乐轻松的学习和成长。让宝宝在数学这辆巴士上快速成长。
    </cn>


    <en>This is a special application for infant design, children's early teaching games, and deep understanding of them! A variety of puzzle games, children's habit training, interest training, but also a new interactive type of literacy card games.
The family education for free children's puzzle games, interactive learning, through pictures, let the baby learn to identify earlier things in life, easy to learn all kinds of animal card and sound... From the Visual Auditory tactile... Three aspects of enlightenment education, let the baby easy cognition in the game.

Simply press, you can see a lot of pictures and hear a variety of sounds. The child's touch, vision and hearing are exercised through more than 100 voices and images that cover animals, instruments, and vehicles. Just click on an animal or an item to look at the image, listen to its name, and look at the spelling. This is a perfect learning tool for the children's game time.

The high definition pictures are bright and vivid, and the sound quality is excellent. We provide 6 kinds of pictures, including domestic animals, wild animals, musical instruments, vehicles, household articles and scenic spots. These wonderful pictures will satisfy children's curiosity and are always cute. Musical instruments can bring a lot of fun. The music that each musical instrument provides, may also let you gently shake it!

－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－－

Game features:
* interactive learning games.
* it's safe and easy to operate, and you can play it lightly.
* a fascinating learning environment for children, including clear and beautiful pictures and interesting sounds.
* paired game: a carefully designed puzzle game for 0-3 - year - old babies to develop a baby's ability to judge.
* rich and interesting products make children think independently, learn freely, and enjoy the fun of exploring the world.


We focus on the children's game products R & D, according to the growth characteristics of different ages of children, children create exclusive products carefully, interactive and unique way, to achieve the purpose and effect of the enlightenment education, added a bright door for the baby's childhood, is conducive to children's healthy physical and mental development, mental development and perfect. In the fun of learning and growth. Let the baby grow fast on the math bus.
    </en>

</root>
