<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
    <cn>这是一款帮助孩子快速认识植物和颜色的早教应用!
包含100多种常见的植物,十几种颜色: 红色, 蓝色, 黄色, 绿色, 橙色, 橙色, 粉色, 紫色, 灰色, 棕色, 黑色, 白色等。让孩子在有趣和直观的拖动物体过程中快速记住和分辨出这些形状和颜色。
游戏包括三种模式：植物，颜色，植物和颜色组合模式，每个模式包含有50多个关卡。
涵盖的植物有：
蔬菜类：白菜 菠菜 油菜 卷心菜 苋菜 韭菜 蒿菜 香菜 芥菜 芥兰 茴香 蒜苗 莴笋 空心菜 生菜 白花菜 西兰花 油麦菜 甘蓝 小葱 萝卜 马铃薯 莲藕 红薯 山药 芋头 苤蓝 慈姑 洋葱 生姜 大蒜 蒜苔 韭菜花 大葱 韭黄 冬瓜 南瓜 西葫芦 丝瓜 黄瓜 茄子 西红柿 苦瓜 辣椒 玉米 毛豆 豌豆 蚕豆 扁豆 四季豆 平菇 香菇  金针菇 木耳 银耳 杏鲍菇 口蘑
花卉类： 梅花 桃花  牡丹 海棠 玉兰 紫荆 连翘  丁香 紫藤 杜鹃花 石榴花 含笑花 白兰花 茉莉花 栀子花 桂花 木芙蓉 腊梅 山茶花 风信子 郁金香 紫罗兰 菊花 荷花 石蒜 水仙 千日红
水果类： 菠萝 草莓 海棠果 哈密瓜 红提 红枣 火龙果 梨 李子 芒果 梅子 木瓜 柠檬 苹果 葡萄 脐橙 黄瓜 山楂 柿子 水晶葡萄 桃子 甜瓜  无花果 乌梅 香瓜 香蕉 西瓜 杏 樱桃 
树木类：珊瑚树 银杏 冬青 女贞 落叶松 柠檬树 合欢树 苏铁 紫薇树 桧柏 杉树 樟树 椴树 桑树 桃树 杨树 柳树 桂花树 梧桐树 榕树 枫树
    </cn>


    <en>This is an early education application to help children quickly recognize plants and colors!
Including more than 100 common plants, more than a dozen colors: red, blue, yellow, green, orange, orange, pink, purple, grey, brown, black, white and so on. Let children quickly remember and distinguish these shapes and colors in the process of interesting and intuitive dragging.
The game consists of three modes: plant, color, plant and color combination modes, each mode contains more than 50 levels.
The plants covered are:
Vegetables: Chinese cabbage, spinach, cabbage, amaranth, leek, artemisia, mustard, mustard, broccoli, garlic seedlings, lettuce, hollow cabbage, broccoli, broccoli, broccoli, scallion, radish, potato, lotus root, sweet potato, yam, taro, lobster, chive, onion, onion, garlic, leek, onion, onion, onion, cucumber, pumpkin, cucumber, cucumber, cucumber, eggplant, tomato, bitter pepper Corn, pea, broad bean, lentil, green bean, mushroom, mushroom, Flammulina velutipes, fungus, tremella, almond, abalone, mushroom and mushroom
Flowers: Plum, peach, peony, begonia, magnolia, bauhinia, forsythia, lilac, rhododendron, pomegranate, michelia, brandy, jasmine, gardenia, osmanthus, hibiscus, camellia, hyacinth, tulip, violet, lotus, garlic, narcissus, thousand-day red
Fruits: Pineapple, strawberry, Begonia, Hami melon, red date, Huolong pear, plum, mango, plum, papaya, lemon, apple, navel, orange, cucumber, persimmon, crystal, grape, peach, melon, fig, melon, banana, watermelon, apricot and cherry
Trees: Coral tree, Ginkgo biloba, Holly Ligustrum, Larix gmelinii, Lemon tree, Albizzia cycas, Lagerstroemia, Cedar fir, Laurel tree, Laurel tree, Mulberry tree, Peach tree, Poplar tree, Willow tree, Osmanthus tree, Ficus tree, Maple tree
    </en>

</root>
