<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
    <cn>这是一款帮助孩子快速学习水果和颜色的应用! 
    这里有美味可口的苹果、香蕉、桃子等，你想吃的水果都有，应有尽有，千万不要错过呦！涵盖的水果有： 浆果类：草莓，蓝莓，黑莓，桑葚，覆盆子，葡萄，青提，红提，水晶葡萄， 马奶子 柑橘类：砂糖橘，金橘，甜橙，脐橙，西柚，柚子，葡萄柚， 柠檬，文旦 核果类：桃子，李子，樱桃，杏，梅子，杨梅， 西梅，乌梅，红枣，海枣，蜜枣，橄榄，荔枝，龙眼（桂圆），槟榔 仁果类：苹果 ，梨 ，蛇果，海棠果，沙果，柿子，山竹，黑布林， 枇杷，杨桃，山楂，圣女果，无花果，白果，罗汉果，火龙果，猕猴桃
瓜类：西瓜，甜瓜，香瓜，哈密瓜，木瓜，乳瓜 其他：菠萝，芒果，板栗，椰子，奇异果，芭乐，榴莲，香蕉，甘蔗， 莲子，石榴，核桃
十几种颜色: 红色, 蓝色, 黄色, 绿色, 橙色, 橙色, 粉色, 紫色, 灰色, 棕色, 黑色, 白色等。让孩子在有趣和直观的拖动过程中快速记住和分辨出这些水果和颜色。
    游戏包括三种模式：水果，颜色，水果和颜色组合模式，每个模式包含有50多个关卡。
    快来和我们一起开始奇妙的水果拼图之旅，一起认识各种各样的水果吧！ 
    </cn>


    <en>This is an application to help children learn fruit and color quickly!
Here are delicious apples, bananas, peaches and so on. You can have all the fruits you want. Don't miss them! Fruits covered include: berries: strawberries, blueberries, blackberries, mulberries, raspberries, grapes, qingti, Hongti, crystal grapes, horse milk citrus: sugar orange, kumquat, sweet orange, navel orange, grapefruit, grapefruit, grapefruit, lemon, Wendan stone fruits: peaches, plums, cherries, apricots, plums, bayberry, Prunus mume, Prunus mume, red jujube, sea jujube, honey jujube, olive, litchi, longan (longan), areca kernel: apple, pear, snake fruit, Begonia fruit, sand fruit, persimmon, mangosteen, black cloth forest, loquat, carambola, hawthorn, virgin fruit, figs, white fruit, Luohanguo, huolongguo, kiwifruit
Melons: watermelon, melon, cantaloupe, Hami melon, papaya, papaya others: pineapple, mango, chestnut, coconut, kiwi fruit, guava, durian, banana, sugarcane, lotus seed, pomegranate, walnut
Dozens of colors: red, blue, yellow, green, orange, orange, pink, purple, gray, brown, black, white, etc. Let children quickly remember and distinguish these fruits and colors in the process of interesting and intuitive dragging.
The game includes three modes: fruit, color, fruit and color combination mode, each mode contains more than 50 levels.
Come and join us to start a wonderful fruit puzzle journey, and get to know all kinds of fruits together!
    </en>

</root>
