<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
    <cn>这是一款平板上儿童早教寻宝学校软件！农场里有各种可爱的植物，等着孩子们去发现哦，统统找出来即可完成任务。
启发孩子的想象力、记忆力、创造力，开发智力；宝贝们，快来农场一起寻找植物吧!
涵盖的植物有：
蔬菜类：白菜 菠菜 油菜 卷心菜 苋菜 韭菜 蒿菜 香菜 芥菜 芥兰 茴香 蒜苗 莴笋 空心菜 生菜 白花菜 西兰花 油麦菜 甘蓝 小葱 萝卜 马铃薯 莲藕 红薯 山药 芋头 苤蓝 慈姑 洋葱 生姜 大蒜 蒜苔 韭菜花 大葱 韭黄 冬瓜 南瓜 西葫芦 丝瓜 黄瓜 茄子 西红柿 苦瓜 辣椒 玉米 毛豆 豌豆 蚕豆 扁豆 四季豆 平菇 香菇  金针菇 木耳 银耳 杏鲍菇 口蘑
花卉类： 梅花 桃花  牡丹 海棠 玉兰 紫荆 连翘  丁香 紫藤 杜鹃花 石榴花 含笑花 白兰花 茉莉花 栀子花 桂花 木芙蓉 腊梅 山茶花 风信子 郁金香 紫罗兰 菊花 荷花 石蒜 水仙 千日红
水果类： 菠萝 草莓 海棠果 哈密瓜 红提 红枣 火龙果 梨 李子 芒果 梅子 木瓜 柠檬 苹果 葡萄 脐橙 黄瓜 山楂 柿子 水晶葡萄 桃子 甜瓜  无花果 乌梅 香瓜 香蕉 西瓜 杏 樱桃 
树木类：珊瑚树 银杏 冬青 女贞 落叶松 柠檬树 合欢树 苏铁 紫薇树 桧柏 杉树 樟树 椴树 桑树 桃树 杨树 柳树 桂花树 梧桐树 榕树 枫树

    </cn>


    <en>This is a children's early childhood education treasure hunt school software on the Pad! There are all kinds of lovely plants in the farm, waiting for the children to find them, and then they can complete the task.
Inspire children's imagination, memory, creativity and intelligence; come to the farm to find plants, babies!
The plants covered are:
Vegetables: cabbage, spinach, rape, cabbage, amaranth, leek, Artemisia, coriander, mustard, fennel, garlic, lettuce, cabbage, cauliflower, broccoli, oatmeal, cabbage, shallot, radish, radish, potato, lotus root, sweet potato, yam, taro, taro, arrowhead, onion, ginger, garlic, garlic, leek, leek, winter melon, pumpkin, squash, cucumber, eggplant, tomato, bitter melon, pepper Corn, pea, broad bean, lentil, four season bean, mushroom, mushroom, Flammulina mushroom, fungus, tremella, apricot, abalone, mushroom, Tricholoma
Flowers: plum, peach, peony, Begonia, Magnolia, Bauhinia, forsythia, lilac, wisteria, Rhododendron, pomegranate, smiley, Magnolia, jasmine, gardenia, osmanthus, hibiscus, wintersweet, camellia, hyacinth, tulip, violet, chrysanthemum, lotus, Lycoris, Narcissus
Fruits: pineapple, strawberry, Begonia, Hami melon, red date, huolongguo, pear, plum, mango, plum, papaya, lemon, apple, grape, navel orange, cucumber, hawthorn, persimmon, crystal, peach, melon, figs, black plum, melon, melon, melon, watermelon, apricot, cherry
Trees: ginkgo, ginkgo, holly, privet, larch, lemon, tree, tree, tree, tree, tree, Lagerstroemia, cedar, cedar, camphor, Tilia, mulberry, peach, poplar, willow, osmanthus, Wutong, fig, maple.
    </en>

</root>
