<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root> 
    <cn>这是一款练字的早教学习软件。
汉字书写能力的培养是宝宝学前或者小学教育中非常重要的一环，不同的父母能力和培养方式都不一样，造成孩子入学之后的学习水平千差万别。本应用正是为孩子练习汉字笔画的书写而设计的，通过汉字笔画的学习 能够令孩子清楚的知道汉字的落笔、笔划的方向及次序等，可视化地抄写中文增强对汉字的视觉记忆 ,并配有每个汉字的普通话和粤语读音以及相应的图片说明，是孩子们学习汉字的好帮手，赶快来下载体验吧！
我们产品的特点：
1，孩子可以方便的观看汉字笔画书写动画和顺序示意图。
2，笔画书写错误会自动擦除，操作非常简单和便利。
3，自动保存孩子的练字记录，方便查看过往的练字效果。
4，精选常用的汉字，让您的可爱宝宝练个不停。
5，每个汉字都配有对应的图片，让孩子形象地领悟汉字的含义，同时配有中文普通话和广东话真人发音。
6，我们产品的开发人员本身也是孩子的家长，更加关心孩子的成长，同时我们也请来了育儿专家一起来设计这款应用。
    </cn>


    <en>This is a learning software on the calligraphy education.
The ability to write Chinese characters is a very important part of preschool or primary school education, different parents' ability and ways of training are different, resulting in different levels of learning after children enter school. This application is designed for children to practice writing strokes Chinese characters, through learning can make children Chinese characters strokes know the direction of the stroke, strokes Chinese characters and sequence, copying Chinese Chinese characters to enhance visualization of visual memory, and with each of the Mandarin and Cantonese pronunciation Chinese characters and the corresponding diagrams. The children are learning a good helper Chinese characters, as soon as possible to download experience!
The characteristics of our products:
1, the children can easily watch Chinese character strokes, write animation and sequence diagram.
2, stroke writing errors will automatically erase, the operation is very simple and convenient.
3, automatically save the children's writing record, writing effect easy to view the past.
4, select the commonly used Chinese characters, let your lovely baby practice non-stop.
5, each Chinese character is equipped with a corresponding picture, so that children understand the meaning of Chinese characters vividly, with Mandarin Chinese and Cantonese pronunciation.
6, our product developers themselves are also the parents of children, more concerned about the growth of children, while we also invited parenting experts together to design this application.
    </en>

</root>
