<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
    <cn>
    成语是中华文化的灵魂，源远流长，寓意深远。
    本词典(平板版本)支持离线查询，收录成语2万多条，从词条注解、出处说明、名家示例等多维度诠释成语的来龙去脉。成语大全支持通配符查询，释义精炼的同时配以出处说明，及历代名家对成语的自如使用，即学习了成语又陶冶了情操
    它是一部规范、详尽与简明兼顾、功能与经典并举，深受广大读者欢迎的成语大词典。
    功能说明：
    本词典通过以下几种方式检索
    1.按成语部分检索
    通过依次输入成语部分检索，比如输入：\'表里\' 检索到 表里如一;输入\'如一\' 检索 表里如一；输入\'表?里?一\' 检索 表里如一。
    2.按字母检索
    通过依次输入组成成语的一个或多个字的首字母检索，比如输入：BLRY 检索成语 表里如一;
    3.按拼音检索
    通过依次输入组成成语的一或多个字的拼音检索，用空格分隔，比如输入：biao li ru yi 检索成语 表里如一;
    4.按词形检索
    通过输入成语的构词形式来检索，比如输入 AABB 检索到类似 安安稳稳、风风火火等，输入AABC 检索到 比比皆是、楚楚可怜等成语。</cn>


    <en> Idioms are the soul of Chinese culture, with a long history and profound meaning.
This dictionary (Pad version) supports offline query and contains more than 20000 idioms. It interprets the origin and development of Idioms from multiple dimensions, such as term annotation, source description, famous experts' examples, etc. The idiom Daquan supports wildcard query, refined interpretation, and explanation of the source, as well as the free use of idioms by famous scholars of all ages. It not only learns idioms, but also cultivates sentiment
It is a standard, detailed and concise dictionary of idioms, with both functions and classics, which is popular among readers.
Function Description:
This dictionary is searched in the following ways
1. Search by idiom
Search by inputting idioms in turn, for example, input: "in the table \" to search for the same in the table; input "as one \" to search for the same in the table; input "in the table" as one \ "to search for the same in the table.
2. Search by letter
Search by inputting the first letter of one or more words that make up the idiom in turn, for example, input: blry searches for the same idiom list;
3. Search by pinyin
By inputting the Pinyin of one or more words that make up the idiom in turn, and separating them with spaces, for example, inputting: Biao Li Ru Yi searches the idiom for the same list;
4. Search by word form
By inputting the word formation form of idioms to retrieve, for example, inputting AABB to retrieve idioms like safe, stable, popular, etc., inputting AABC to retrieve idioms everywhere and pathetic.</en>

</root>
