<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
    <cn>
   这是一款平板上简单的儿童早教软件，画面流畅！玩法简单，只要猜出图片中的植物名字即可！屏幕上会出现各种植物，应有尽有。 可以大幅提高宝宝识别生活中常见的事物，同时也可以提高对汉字的学习，是妈妈们早教的好帮手！宝宝们赶快来体验吧！
 每一种植物有高清的图片和朗朗上口的读音。小朋友一定会很感兴趣。 快来和我们一起开始奇妙的植物猜图之旅吧。
涵盖的植物有：
蔬菜类：白菜 菠菜 油菜 卷心菜 苋菜 韭菜 蒿菜 香菜 芥菜 芥兰 茴香 蒜苗 莴笋 空心菜 生菜 白花菜 西兰花 油麦菜 甘蓝 小葱 萝卜 马铃薯 莲藕 红薯 山药 芋头 苤蓝 慈姑 洋葱 生姜 大蒜 蒜苔 韭菜花 大葱 韭黄 冬瓜 南瓜 西葫芦 丝瓜 黄瓜 茄子 西红柿 苦瓜 辣椒 玉米 毛豆 豌豆 蚕豆 扁豆 四季豆 平菇 香菇  金针菇 木耳 银耳 杏鲍菇 口蘑
花卉类： 梅花 桃花  牡丹 海棠 玉兰 紫荆 连翘  丁香 紫藤 杜鹃花 石榴花 含笑花 白兰花 茉莉花 栀子花 桂花 木芙蓉 腊梅 山茶花 风信子 郁金香 紫罗兰 菊花 荷花 石蒜 水仙 千日红
水果类： 菠萝 草莓 海棠果 哈密瓜 红提 红枣 火龙果 梨 李子 芒果 梅子 木瓜 柠檬 苹果 葡萄 脐橙 黄瓜 山楂 柿子 水晶葡萄 桃子 甜瓜  无花果 乌梅 香瓜 香蕉 西瓜 杏 樱桃 
树木类：珊瑚树 银杏 冬青 女贞 落叶松 柠檬树 合欢树 苏铁 紫薇树 桧柏 杉树 樟树 椴树 桑树 桃树 杨树 柳树 桂花树 梧桐树 榕树 枫树

    </cn>


    <en>This is a simple early childhood education software on the Pad, smooth screen! Play simple, as long as you guess the name of the plant in the picture! All kinds of plants will appear on the screen. It can greatly improve the baby's recognition of common things in life, and also improve the learning of Chinese characters. It's a good helper for mothers to teach early! Let's experience it quickly!
Every plant has high-definition pictures and catchy pronunciation. Children will be very interested. Come and join us on a wonderful journey of plant guessing.
The plants covered are:
Vegetables: cabbage, spinach, rape, cabbage, amaranth, leek, Artemisia, coriander, mustard, fennel, garlic, lettuce, cabbage, cauliflower, broccoli, oatmeal, cabbage, shallot, radish, radish, potato, lotus root, sweet potato, yam, taro, taro, arrowhead, onion, ginger, garlic, garlic, leek, leek, winter melon, pumpkin, squash, cucumber, eggplant, tomato, bitter melon, pepper Corn, pea, broad bean, lentil, four season bean, mushroom, mushroom, Flammulina mushroom, fungus, tremella, apricot, abalone, mushroom, Tricholoma
Flowers: plum, peach, peony, Begonia, Magnolia, Bauhinia, forsythia, lilac, wisteria, Rhododendron, pomegranate, smiley, Magnolia, jasmine, gardenia, osmanthus, hibiscus, wintersweet, camellia, hyacinth, tulip, violet, chrysanthemum, lotus, Lycoris, Narcissus
Fruits: pineapple, strawberry, Begonia, Hami melon, red date, huolongguo, pear, plum, mango, plum, papaya, lemon, apple, grape, navel orange, cucumber, hawthorn, persimmon, crystal, peach, melon, figs, black plum, melon, melon, melon, watermelon, apricot, cherry
Trees: ginkgo, ginkgo, holly, privet, larch, lemon, tree, tree, tree, tree, tree, Lagerstroemia, cedar, cedar, camphor, Tilia, mulberry, peach, poplar, willow, osmanthus, Wutong, fig, maple.
    </en>

</root>
